testony.com 2018-03-07

# 

1.

**Objective and responsible authority**

1.1.
    This Privacy Policy clarifies the nature, scope and purpose of collecting, processing (hereinafter referred to as „processing“) and using data within our services and the connected websites, functions and contents (hereinafter referred to as „Service“ or „Website“), independent of the domains, systems, platforms and devices (e.g. desktops or portable devices) used to operate our Service. 
1.2.
    Service provider and the authority responsible for data processing is social sweethearts GmbH, Landsberger Str. 155, Building 4 / 3. Floor, D - 80687 München (Munich), Germany, legal and contact information: [http://www.socialsweethearts.de/en_US/imprint](https://www.socialsweethearts.de/en_US/imprint), (hereinafter referred to as „we“ or „us’). 
1.3.
     The term „user“ means all customers and visitors of our online offers and Service. The terms used here, e.g. „user“, are gender neutral. 
1.4.
     If the Privacy Policy contains consent clauses, these are to be highlighted 
1.5.
     In addition to this Privacy Policy our Terms of Service apply: [http://www.socialsweethearts.de/terms_en.html](https://www.socialsweethearts.de/terms_en.html). 
1.6.
    Data protection officer: Dr. Thomas Schwenke, Paul-Lincke-Ufer 42/43, 10999 Berlin, E-Mail: [DSB@extern.socialsweethearts.de](mailto:D%53%42@e%78t%65%72n.soc%69alsweet%68ea%72t%73.%64%65). 
2.

**Definitions**

2.1.
    **Personally Identifiable Data** \- This kind of data can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual (e.g. names, e-mail-addresses). 
2.2.
    **Pseudonymous Data** \- The pseudonymous data identifies a holder, that is, one or more human beings who possess but do not disclose their true names (e.g. "user5623"). 
2.3.
    **Cookies** \- A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while a user is browsing a website. When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user's previous activity. We use Cookies in order to improve the usability of our services as well as for analyzing and personalizing purposes. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively accept certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, there may some features of our site that will not be available to you and some web pages may not display properly. You may opt-out from many ad-serving cookies by using the services provided by <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> or <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices/> for users form the European Union or <http://youradchoices.ca/choices> for users from Canada or <http://youronlinechoices.com.au/> for users from Australia. 
2.4.
    **Web beacons** \- Web beacons (also known as Pixel Tags) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page for the purpose of transferring information, such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (uniform resource locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. 
2.5.
    **IP Address** \- An Internet Protocol address (IP address) is a numerical label assigned to each device (e.g., computer, printer) participating in the Internet. We store the IP address only, if it is necessary to provide a service or if may be legally necessary. 
3.

**Essential information for data processing and security**

3.1.
    We will process personally identifiable data within the scope of the law and not without your required further consent only to the extent necessary for the conclusion and execution of our contractual relationship. 
3.2.
    We take organizational, contractual and technical security measures to ensure that the provisions of data privacy laws are complied with and, as a result, the data managed by us is protected from accidental or intentional manipulations, loss, destruction or access by unauthorized persons. These security measures are monitored on a regular basis and updated according to industry standard as necessary. 
3.3.
    If, within the framework of this Privacy Policy, contents, tools or other means and mediums are used by other providers (hereinafter referred to collectively as “Third-party Providers”) and whose registered office is abroad, it is assumed that a data transfer to the countries where those registered offices of the Third-party Providers are located takes place. The transmission of data to third-party countries is either based on legal authorization, user consent or specific clauses in the contract, which provide for legally required data security. 
4.

**Processing of personal data**

4.1.
    Personal data, in addition to the use expressly named in this agreement and allowed by law, is used for the following purposes: 

  * The provision, maintenance, security and execution of our Service;
  * Ensuring effective customer Service and technical support

4.2.
    Upon contacting us, information is saved for the purpose of processing the request and for the event that follow-up questions arise. 
5.

**Registration through authentication services of third parties**

5.1.
    Users can register and log in by using authentication services of Third-party Providers, as far as these are available (hereinafter referred to as „authentication by a third-party“). Particularly Facebook, Google or Twitter can be possible authentication service providers. 
5.2.
    As requirement for the authentication through a Third-party Provider, users should be registered at the respective Third-party Provider and enter the necessary login details in the appropriate web formula or should be already logged in to the Third-party Provider. 
5.3.
    In the context of a registration, we receive a user ID with the information under which the user with this user ID is logged in and an ID that cannot be further used by the Service Provider (so called “user handle”). Whether we receive further data depends only on the user who uses the authentication by a Third-party Provider, the data that is selected to be released in the context of the authentication, and which data has been authorized by the user in the privacy or other settings of the user account at the Third-party Provider. The data can differ, depending on the provider and the selections of the user; normally these are the e-mail address and the user name. In case of Facebook, this is also the - so called - Public Profile Information, that can be seen by everyone. This includes the name, profile and cover picture, gender, networks (i.e. school or working place), user name (Facebook URL) and user identification number (Facebook ID). 
5.4.
    The password that has been entered in the context of the authentication by a Third-party Provider cannot be seen by us, neither can it be saved by the Service Provider. 
5.5.
    The users are asked to keep in mind that their data, which we save, can be compared and synchronized with their user account at the Third-party Provider automatically. There is no obligation however for us to update the data. 
5.6.
    In the case that users decide that they do not wish to further use the connection of their user account at the Third-party Provider for the authentication by a Third-party Provider, they must cancel this connection within their user account at the Third-party Provider. If the users wish to delete their data we save, they must cancel their account at our Service. 
5.7.
    During the use of authentication by a third party, the users are asked to keep in mind the applicable Terms of Use, as well as the Rules for Data Use of the third party. These can be found: Twitter (<https://twitter.com/tos>, <https://twitter.com/privacy>), Google ([http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/)), Facebook (<https://www.facebook.com/policies/>). 
6.

**ADVERTISEMENT CONSENT**

6.1.
    **You agree with receiving notifications on following topics and with following content via electronic channels, like e-mail and/or push messages related to: test drives, cars, product samples, free coupons, sweepstakes, discount offers, credits or loans, finances, insurances, travel, applications, social media, editorial content and offers, quizzes, personality tests, smartphones, videos, mobile games & applications, newsletters, toolbars, browser add-ons, software, insurances, investments, dating, mobile communications, complimentary tickets, gifts, online games, travel deals, newspapers, magazines, special offers, sim cards, games, electricity, energy related offers, telecommunication services, surveys, market research, fashion, cosmetics, photo products, mail orders, imaging products.**
6.2.
    **This advertisement consent applies within the countries of European Union only after an explicit consent was given within a permission dialogue. The same is true for other jurisdictions, where an explicit consent is required.**
6.3.
    **YOUR BENEFITS: Because of our relations and connections we are able to provide you with offers under beneficial conditions you would otherwise not be able to obtain.**
6.4.
    **DISCLAIMER: Of course, you may at any time opt out from our Service.**
7.

**Newsletter and Personalization**

7.1.
    Newsletters and further electronically sent information (hereafter uniformly referred to as „newsletter”) that are not service-related, are not fulfilling our duties to perform our Service and contain advertisement will only be sent to you, if you have given us your prior consent or if it is permitted by law. 
7.2.
    We may ask you for an opt-in within our Service and sent you an email asking you to confirm your registration (so called double-opt-in). 
7.3.
    Non-promotional and thus no newsletter information includes notifications that are sent within the scope of the contract or business relations. This includes, for example, the sending of service emails with technical or organizational information within the framework of our provision of services, billing information, information concerning technical and legal changes, and questions regarding orders. 
7.4.
    If you no longer want to receive our newsletter you can opt to stop receiving it at any time. Opt-out possibilities are included in each mail and may also be changed within your account settings. 
7.5.
    **You also give us the consent to store your IP addresses and the timestamp as part of the sign-up process.** We are legally bound to record the log-on process so as to be able to verify that logging on is done in accordance with regulations. 
7.6.
    **In order to tailor our newsletter to your interests and to avoid contents that are irrelevant for you or to adjust the frequency of our information (i.e. lower the sending frequency, if you open them less), we measure whether you open our newsletter (this with help of a Web Beacon, a small image within the content of the newsletter) and which links you click (this by a link redirection via our servers). We do not use this information for other purposes and we will delete the personally to you related measurement data as soon, as you opt out from receiving our newsletter. This consent applies within the countries of European Union only after an explicit consent was given within a permission dialogue. The same is true for other jurisdictions, where an explicit consent is required.**
8.

**Server Log-Files**

8.1.
    During every visit of our Service information about IP address, access-provider, referring URL, date/time, browser type and version and operating system, amount and state of transferred data is stored in the web server log files. 
8.2.
    We use the log data without any other personal or pseudonymous profiling as required by law only for the purpose of the operation, security and optimization of our servers. 
9.

**Browser notifications**

9.1.
    We enable users to obtain information about our Service and its contents through messages that are shown by their browsers (so called „push notifications”). In order to do this, we currently use the services provided by OneSignal Inc., 201 San Antonio Rd #140, Mountain View, CA 94040, USA. 
9.2.
    The push notifications are set up with the users’ consent and the users’ browser must support such push notifications. In order to be able to display push notifications, OneSignal is required to store an identifying feature of the browser, which is then used for push notifications only. 
9.3.
    Users can find more information about push notifications in OneSignal’s privacy policy: <https://onesignal.com/privacy_policy>. 
9.4.
    Users may object to the further use of our push notifications at any time by disabling the function in their browser settings. 
10.

**Google Analytics and User ID**

10.1.
    We use Google Analytics, a Google Inc. („Google“) web analysis service. Google uses cookies, text files that are saved on users' computers and allow the use of our Service to be analyzed. The information generated on the user's use of our Service by the cookie is generally transferred to a Google server in the US where it is saved. 
10.2.
    We also use the function User ID in order to track data on user interaction with our Service. This User ID is anonymized and encrypted and will be except for its pseudonymous use not be processed with other data of a user in a way that makes the user identifiable. 
10.3.
    Google will use this information on our behalf in order to assess users' use of our Service, in order to compile reports on the activities within our Service and in order to render additional services for us associated with the use of our Service and Internet use. 
10.4.
    We only use Google Analytics with activated IP anonymization. This means that Google shortens user IP addresses within an EU member state or in other contractual states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address transferred to a Google server in the US where it is shortened. 
10.5.
    We use the Analytics features for remarketing, Google Display Network impressions, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and Google Analytics reports on demographics and user interests. You can prevent Google from using Google Analytics for display ads and customize ads on the Google Display Network at: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>. 
10.6.
    The IP address transferred by the user's browser is not linked to other Google data. Users can prevent cookies being saved through the appropriate setting on their browser software; users can also prevent the acquisition of the data generated by the cookie and related to the use of our Service in addition to the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the available browser plug-in at the following link: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 
10.7.
    You can find further information on Google’s use of data for marketing purposes on the site map: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads>, Google’s privacy policy can be viewed at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy>. If you wish to object to the collection of data by Google Marketing Services, you can use the settings and opt-out functions provided by Google: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences). 
11.

**Google Re/Marketing Services**

11.1.
     We use the marketing and remarketing services (hereinafter jointly referred to as the „Google Re/Marketing Services”) provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA („Google”). 
11.2.
    The Google Re/Marketing Services enable us to display ads for and on our Websites and Service in a more targeted manner so that users are only shown ads which might actually be of interest to them. Where users are, for example, shown ads for products in which they were interested on other websites, this is known as „remarketing”. For this purpose, as soon as the user accesses our Websites, or other websites on which Google Re/Marketing Services have been activated, Google immediately executes a Google code and so called re/marketing tags (invisible graphics or code, also called Web Beacons) are integrated into the Website. With the help of these tags, an individual cookie, i.e. a small file, is stored on the users’ device (comparable technology can be used instead of cookies). The cookies can be set from various domains, including google.com, doubleclick.net, invitemedia.com, admeld.com, googlesyndication.com or googleadservices.com. This file keeps a record of which websites the user visits, what content he/she is interested in and which offers he/she has clicked on, as well as technical information about the browser and operating system, referring websites, time of access and other details about the use of the website content. The users’ IP address is also recorded, whereby we, within the context of Google Analytics, would like to point out that, within member states of the European Union or in other countries that are party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area, the IP address is truncated and only transmitted in its entirety to a Google server in the US and truncated there in exceptional cases. The IP address will not be linked with any of the user’s data from other services offered by Google. The aforementioned information can also be combined with equivalent information from other sources. If the user visits other websites afterwards, he/she can only be shown the ads that directly reflect his/her interests. 
11.3.
    Within the scope of Google Re/Marketing Services, the users’ data is processed pseudonymously. This means that Google does not, for example, store and process the users’ name or e-mail address, instead processing the relevant data on the basis of the cookies within pseudonymous user profiles. In other words, from Google’s point of view, the ads are managed and displayed for the cookie owner, regardless of who the cookie owner is, rather than for a specifically identified person. This shall not apply where the user has expressly permitted Google to process the data without this pseudonymization. The information collected about the users via „DoubleClick” shall be transmitted to Google and stored on Google’s servers in the US. 
11.4.
    The online advertising program „Google AdWords” is just one of the Google Re/Marketing Services used by us. In the case of Google AdWords, each AdWords customer is given a different „conversion cookie”. This means that cookies cannot be tracked on the websites of AdWords customers. The information obtained through the cookies serves to create conversion statistics for AdWords customers who have opted for conversion tracking. The AdWords customers find out the total number of users who have clicked on their ad and have been forwarded to a webpage into which a conversion tracking tag has been integrated. However, they do not receive any information that would allow users to be personally identified. 
11.5.
    On the basis of Google Re/Marketing Services, we integrate third-party „DoubleClick“ ads. DoubleClick uses cookies that enable Google and its partner websites to run ads based on users visiting this or other websites. 
11.6.
    On the basis of Google Re/Marketing Services, we also integrate third-party „AdSense“ ads. AdSense uses cookies that enable Google and its partner websites to run ads based on users visiting this or other websites. 
11.7.
    With the help of Google optimization services, we also test the user-friendliness and effectiveness of our Websites, e.g. by carrying out A/B tests, whereby users are shown different versions of Websites. 
11.8.
    Other Google Re/Marketing Services we use, are the „Campaign Manager” and the „Google Tag Manager”, which enable us to integrate other Google Analytics and Marketing Services into our Website (e.g. „AdWords”, „DoubleClick” or „Google Analytics”). 
11.9.
    You can find further information on Google’s use of data for marketing purposes on the site map: <https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads>, Google’s privacy policy can be viewed at <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy>. 
11.10.
    If you wish to object to the collection of data by Google Re/Marketing Services, you can use the settings and opt-out functions provided by Google: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences). 
12.

**General information on usage of Facebook**

12.1.
     **If the Service is carried out as a Facebook application and/or if authentication through Facebook is used, the permission of users is required for us to access their stored data on Facebook.**
12.2.
     **Users are expressly referred in the context of the Facebook consent dialog to this data collection and the data shared by Facebook with us (e.g. public profile, friends list, e-mail address and "Like" information) through the Service.**
12.3.
     **We may use the requested data anonymously for statistical purposes. I.e., if we may access the data on user's facebook chronic, posts or likes, we may evaluate how often a posting was shared or liked in order to help us improve our Services and its contents like our Quizzes and personality tests. We perform the evaluation anonymously, meaning independently of users' Personally Identifiable Data we received with the consent of the user (e.g. without the Facebook-ID). These evaluations are just for us only, without any transfers of this data to third parties.**
12.4.
     Users are referred to Facebook’s privacy policy <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other> for more information about the consent process, consent granted and ways of revoking such consent within their Facebook profile. 
12.5.
     Users have the option in the Facebook application settings to end their use of the Service at any time: <https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=applications>. 
13.

**Individual Content Adjustment**

13.1.
    **We use the information we receive on the user in order to adjust our Service and its contents with user’s demands, expectations or interests, whereby user profiles may be created. For this purpose, we use the data that we receive on users as described within this Privacy Policy and then analyze it via algorithmical functions.**
13.2.
    **This processed information includes data we receive from users during the registration procedure (e.g. a users’ gender, name or country), as well as the data we receive on a user’s use of our Service (e.g. which parts of our Service are preferably used, recommended, favored or shared with other users).**
14.

**Use of Facebook Social Plugins**

14.1.
    Our Service uses social plugins („plugins’) provided by the social network Facebook, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA, or if you live in the European Union, Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Irland („Facebook“). The plugins are usually identifiable by a Facebook logo (e.g. letter f on blue background or a thumb up icon). For a full list of all social Plugins please see <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>. 
14.2.
    When you visit a page of our Service that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser that embeds the latter into the Service, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the respective page of our Service. Thus, we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge: The embedded plugins provide Facebook with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our Service. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking „Like”, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Facebook, there is possibility that the plugins transmit your IP-address to Facebook. 
14.3.
    For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Facebook’s privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. 
14.4.
    In case you want to opt out of being subject to Facebook's use of your data for marketing purposes please use Facebook's opt-out settings provided within your user profile: <https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads> or the opt-out possibilities on the websites <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or for users from the EU [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Your choices are irrespective of platforms and devices and will be considered while using desktop or mobile devices. 
15.

**Facebook Re/Marketing, App-Analytics and Audience Network**

15.1.
    Within our Service we use the „Facebook Pixel“, the „App Analytics” functions and advertising contents of the Audience Network (hereinafter jointly referred to as the „Facebook Re/Marketing Functions”) provided by the social network Facebook, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA, or if you live in the European Union, Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Irland („Facebook“). The Facebook Re/Marketing Functions allow us and Facebook to determine the relevant target audiences, in order to display advertisements (hereinafter referred to as „Facebook-Ads’) in reference to potential interests of the users who visited our Service, as well as to users with similar attributes (so called “Lookalike Audiences”). We use the Facebook Re/Marketing Functions, because we want to display Facebook-Ads only to users, who displayed an interest in our Service. The Facebook Re/Marketing Functions allow us and Facebook to determine, whether our Ads were effective and satisfactory for users by being able to comprehend users’ actions, after they were forwarded to our Service by clicking a Facebook-Ad. 
15.2.
    When you visit our Service or other websites that are member of Facebook’s Audience Network and display Ads, that include or use Facebook Re/Marketing Functions, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the Facebook Re/Marketing Functions content to your browser which embeds the latter into our Service, enabling Facebook to receive the relevant information and storing a cookie (or similar device related characteristics, especially for the App Analytics functions) on your device. The cookie allows Facebook to store the relevant information within your device and retrieve it for the above-mentioned purposes, whereby user profiles may be created. 
15.3.
    The data Facebook collects is anonymous to us, thus does not reveal any personally identifiable information on you. However, Facebook may connect the data with your user profile within its network. Facebook processes your data in accordance with its privacy policy, therefore you'll get there more information on the Facebook Re/Marketing Functions and generally on Facebook Ads: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>. 
15.4.
    In case you want to opt out of being subject to our and Facebook's use of Facebook Re/Marketing Functions for marketing purposes please use Facebook's opt-out settings provided within your user profile: <https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads> or the opt-out possibilities on the websites <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or for users from the EU [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Your choices are irrespective of platforms and devices and will be considered while using desktop or mobile device. 
16.

**Mobile Statistics and ad Services**

16.1.
    We use Flurry (www.flurry.com 360 3rd Street San Francisco, CA 94107, USA) to track and report on the usage and browsing patterns on our mobile applications, whereby user profiles may be created. For more information about Flurry and its privacy policy, please go to <http://www.flurry.com/about-us/legal/privacy.html>. Flurry may record the type of device and operating system you are using, general location information, as well as events that occur within our apps, such as how often you use our apps. You may opt-out from Flurry: <http://www.flurry.com/user-opt-out.html>. 
16.2.
    Within mobile applications we use Services provided by Applift (<http://www.applift.com/>) and AddApptr (<http://www.addapptr.com/>) in order to improve the usability of our Service as well as for analyzing and advertising purposes, whereby user profiles may be created. The gathered information is stored pseudonymously. That applies for device identification numbers as well as IP-addresses. 
16.3.
    In order to provide push messages, we store a pseudonymous device token that allows us to identify a certain device. 
17.

**Additional Third-Party Analytics and Re/Marketing Tools**

17.1.
    Within our Service we embed third-party (hereinafter „Re/Marketing Provider”) remarketing and ad technology, in order to improve the efficiency of our marketing efforts and the relevance of the advertising presented to consumers, as well as for marketing of advertising space within our Service, whereby user profiles may be created. Re/Marketing Provider might use „Pixel-Tags” (small invisible images, also known as „Web Beacons”) to collect information. Through the use of Pixel-Tags simple actions such as the visitor traffic to the Website can be pseudonymously recorded and collected. The pseudonymous information might also be stored in cookies on your device, includes technical information like your Browser or OS, details of how you used our Service and interacted with contents displayed by the Re/Marketing Provider. This information might be combined with such data collected on other sources or used in order to display user tailored advertising content on other websites and within other services. 
17.2.
    In the following, we will inform you on the Re/Marketing Provider we work with, their privacy policy with detailed information on their data collection and ways to opt-out from their data collection. 

  * Criteo SA, 32 Rue Blanche, 75009 Paris, France. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: <http://www.criteo.com/privacy/>
  * LifeStreet Corporation, 981 Industrial Road, Suite F, San Carlos, CA 94070, USA. Privacy Policy:<http://www.lifestreetmedia.com/privacy/> & Opt-Out: <http://www.lifestreetmedia.com/optout/>
  * Taboola, Inc., Kings Court, 2-16 Goodge Street, 2nd fl., London W1T 2QA, UK. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: [https://www.taboola.com/privacy-policy](http://www.outbrain.com/de/legal/privacy)
  * Outbrain Inc., 39 West 13th Street, 3rd floor, New York, NY 10011, USA. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: <http://www.outbrain.com/de/legal/privacy>
  * OpenX Software Ltd., 4300 Bohannon Dr, 100, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: [http://openx.com/legal/privacypolicy/](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacypolicy/)
  * Revcontent, LLC., 5901 N Honore Ave #210, Sarasota, FL 34243, USA. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: <http://faq.revcontent.com/support/solutions/articles/5000615200-revcontent-s-privacy-policy>
  * Appnexus, Inc., 28 west 23rd street, floor 4, New York, NY 10010 (hereinafter “Appnexus”) Privacy Policy: <https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy-de> Opt-Out: <https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy-de#choices>
  * Statcounter, StatCounter, Guinness Enterprise Centre, Taylor's Lane Dublin 8, Ireland. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: <https://statcounter.com/about/legal/>

18.

**Third-Party Content and Service Provider**

18.1.
    We are using third-party content and service providing services in order to embed their contents like quizzes, tests, games, texts, images, videos or fonts within our Website (hereinafter jointly referred to as the „Content”). This always presupposes that the Third-party Provider uses the user’s IP address. This is because without the IP address, they cannot send the Content to the respective user’s browser. The IP address is thus required for displaying this Content. We endeavor only to use Content of which the respective Third-party Provider uses the IP address only for distributing the Content. Third-party Providers might also use Pixel-Tags (small invisible images, also known as „Web Beacons") to collect information for statistical or marketing purposes. Through the use of Pixel-Tags simple actions such as the visitor traffic to the Website can be pseudonymously recorded and collected, whereby user profiles may be created. The pseudonymous information might also be stored in cookies on your device, includes technical information like your Browser or OS, details of how you used our Service and interacted with Contents displayed by the Third-party Provider. This information might be combined with such data collected on other sources. 
18.2.
    In in the following, we will inform you on the Third-party Provider we work with, their privacy policy with detailed information on their data collection and ways to opt-out from their data collection. 

  * Playbuzz Ltd., Content Provider, 26th Floor Rubinstein Building, 37 Menachem Begin Rd, Tel Aviv, Israel, 6522042. Privacy Policy & Opt-Out: <http://www.playbuzz.com/PrivacyPolicy>
  * Cloudflare, Inc., 101 Townsend St, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA, <https://www.cloudflare.com/>, a Content Delivery Network (CDN), which helps us to deliver contents of our Service faster, especially big media files like images or scripts using a world-wide distributed server network. Cloudflare also helps us to determine on the basis of the IP-address the probable country of a user, in order to adjust our Service and contents to the local requirements (e.g. customs or legal needs). Privacy Policy: <https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/>. 
  * Optimizely, 631 Howard Street, Suite 100 San Francisco, CA 94105, USA, Optimizely allows us to test how changes of our Website (i.e. size of input forms, graphics, font sizes) are perceived by our users (so called „A/B-Testing“). Only for these testing purposes Optimizely sets cookies on user's Devices. Optimizely does not store IP address or any other personally identifiable information. By the nature of its Service, Optimizely will gather non-personally identifiable statistics about the usage of our Website and store that information. Optimizely will not share this website statistics without your consent. Privacy Policy: <https://www.optimizely.com/privacy>, Opt-Out: <https://www.optimizely.com/opt_out>. 
  * Sentry, Inc., 25 Kearny St, Suite 500 San Francisco, CA 94108, USA. Real-time error tracking and analysis. Privacy Policy: <https://sentry.io/privacy/>. 
  * YouTube, Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, video-content, Privacy Policy: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/> , Opt-Out: <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/>. 
  * LittleThings, 21 Penn Plaza 5th Floor New York, New York 10001, USA. Videos, images, texts, etc. Privacy Policy: <http://www.littlethings.com/privacy>. 
  * Spot.IM, New York 620 W 42nd, New York NY 10036, USA. Community tool for online conversation, e.g. enabling users writing comments. By using Spot.IM users consent to the processing of their data as stated in the terms and privacy policy of Spot.IM, which are displayed in the Spot.IM dialog box. Privacy Policy and information on Opt-Out: <https://www.spot.im/privacy/>. 

19.

**Image processing with FaceApp**

We use the services of the provider FaceApp (wireless lab OOO 16 Avtovskaya 401 Saint-Petersburg, 198096, Russia, https://www.faceapp.com, privacy policy: https://www.faceapp.com/privacy) to process photographs uploaded by users. FaceApp analyzes the photographs and edits them according to the functions selected by the users (e. g. prediction of how the person depicted will look in old age). 

The processing of the user's personal data resulting from the photograph is carried out by FaceApp for the sole purpose of the selected function. The photograph is only temporarily stored temporarily for this purpose and is then deleted within five days. Data other than the photograph will not be transmitted to FaceApp. The data is transmitted via an interface to FaceApp, so that FaceApp itself cannot collect any further user data (e. g. no IP address, cookies, etc.). 

With the use of Faceapp, users must agree to the processing of their data as described here in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a, Art. 7 DSGVO. 

The use of the functions is only permitted for users who have reached the minimum age required for consent. The minimum age is generally 16 years (Art. 8 para. 1 DSGVO), but may be lower or higher in accordance with the regulations of individual countries. Users will be informed about the minimum age. In order to determine how high the legally permissible minimum age in the country from which the user uses our services, we can use the IP of the users to determine their location. This is done in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. c of the DSGVO in order to fulfil our legal auditing and verification obligations of a permissible consent. 

The notice of objection and revocation as well as on the further user rights according to their citation at the end of this privacy policy apply. 

20.

**Service, Notices and Deletion of Data**

20.1.
    In compliance with legal requirements we will at any time provide you with information on your personally identifiable data stored by us, free of charge and without undue delay. Please refer to the contact information on our Website. 
20.2.
    Furthermore, you are free to revoke the approvals granted by confirming this Privacy Policy, to complain to the competent supervisory authority, as well as correct, erase or block your personally identifiable data at any time and with future effect. 
20.3.
    We delete the stored personal data, as soon as it is not needed for its purposes anymore and as this is in compliance with all legal storage obligations. 
21.

**Amendments of this Privacy Policy**

21.1.
    We may change the Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to changed legal situations or to changes in the Service and in the data processing. However, this only applies to declarations concerning data processing. If users' consent is required or if elements of the Privacy Policy contain provisions concerning the contractual relationship with the users, the changes are only made with the consent of the users. 
21.2.
    Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any new personally identifiable information.
